[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 19]
Are you their new Demon King?
No.
Then why are you here?
Thank you for protecting my whole clan
in the Palace of Abyssal Mirrors.
At the same time,
I also want to tell you something.
What is it?
Aquatic Demons
were once the King of the demon world.
I've investigated it thoroughly.
These demons
killed people outside recently.
They deserve to die.
Accessories should also be punished slightly.
Those who refuse to be moralized
and still want to kill
should be killed without mercy.
The other demons
will serve me as the king,
be restricted by me,
and never cross the line again.
I don't know who your new Demon King is.
But now,
if you don't regard me as the king,
all you can do is waiting to die.
Greetings, Demon King in White.
This
is not up to you.
Immortal, let me
deal with this trifle.
Move.
Liu Shao!
Brother.
It's really you.
You came at the right time.
He's my brother.
Brother.
Who is your brother?
I'm Luo Ge.
Aren't you my brother?
What happened?
Where is the Protection Spell of Marquis Wuyang's Mansion?
Since the Lord died,
no one has reinforced the Protection Spell.
And the demons keep attacking
Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
Today,
the protection spell was broken.
That's why Marquis Wuyang's Mansion suffered this disaster.
Even Captain Fang...
Captain Fang was also killed.
A lot disciples of Marquis Wuyang's Mansion were injured.
Even though we escaped,
we don't know where to go.
If this continues,
the mortal world will become the demons' territory.
Even Marquis Wuyang's Mansion was defeated?
Brother.
Where did he go?
That direction
should be Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
The Protection Spell.
The Protection Spell!
Immortal rebuilt the Protection Spell!
With it,
Marquis Wuyang's Mansion
may emerge again.
That's right.
Yeah.
Yes.
Great!
There's hope.
Let's go.
Come on.
Brother!
Brother.
Well...
Rebuilt the Protection Spell?
How much immortal energy did it take?
It's stronger than the Lord's Protection Spell.
I'm truly in awe.
If you want to do it,
there's nothing you can't do.
Okay.
One day,
I will regain the reputation of Marquis Wuyang's Mansion
and become the master of the mortal world,
making the mortal world free from demons
and become a peaceful world.
Stop bragging.
Look at you, Xue.
Why don't you trust me?
Look, the Protection Spell has been rebuilt.
Indeed.
He Na
is also an interesting person who matches your temperament.
I guess so.
Who would believe that?
You can ask my brother.
Well.
Brother.
My brother left?
Yes.
Steping on lotus,
he went back to Xiyin Mountain in a moment.
Really?
It's just that
he seems angry.
Is it because you
helped He Na escape secretly?
Actually, He Na has helped us a lot.
But
he's now Luo Ge.
He doesn't remember anything about Lu Li.
Sister-in-law.
I finally believe
Immortal Luo Ge
is my brother, Lu Li.
He's much more capable than before
and his temper has changed
but
he's still good at
driving people crazy.
He came by
and protected all of us.
I am sure about my intuition.
It's true that he's good at driving people crazy.
He went back to Xiyin Mountain in an instant.
What should I do?
Should I crawl back on an empty stomach?
How about
go back after eating?
Let's go.
My drumstick is waiting for you.
And...
And trotters, right?
And trotters.
Brother.
Fairy.
Immortal went into seclusion as soon as he came back.
He said he won't see anyone.
Not seeing anyone?
Who are you?
Where is Liu Shao?
I’m the lady-in-waiting sent by the Immortal Master of Palace Wuji
to serve Immortal.
My name is Bai Feng.
Liu Shao is not here.
I guess she's staying in Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
Did she
forget about my matter?
You mean...
It's nothing serious.
But
don't tell them I've been here.
The poison of Brahma Lotus
has been detoxified.
Why hasn't the wound healed yet?
Even the spiritual power
are still weakening.
Immortal.
Are you inside?
Immortal Master sent me to serve you.
Lu Li.
Is that you?
I will get you this time.
Liu Shao.
Get out.
Get out!
Liu Shao.
Liu Shao again.
The person around you
can only be me.
None of them is here.
How boring.
Brother,
I heard you brought a bad guy
back to Xiyin Mountain.
Can I
practice magic
and hit him for fun?
No.
The person is sinister and cunning.
Don't even think about getting close.
I set a restriction
in the place where he is imprisoned.
As long as you get close to him within one inch,
I'll find out soon.
Brother is lying to me again.
There's no restriction at all.
Who is the fairy outside?
Can you chat with me?
Tell me.
What despicable things have you done
that made you arrested?
If I say I'm innocent,
do you believe me?
Fu, General of Water
and the younger brother of the Demon King in White.
If you say you're innocent,
I'm afraid
no one is villain in this world.
You know me?
My brother
never let me know about the demon world
since I was little,
as if I have a grudge against the demon world.
But if I want to know,
there's nothing I can't know.
Not only do I know you,
I also know
you are totally different from your brother.
You
are called General of Water
but you don't usually use water as weapon.
Your weapon is a curved knife.
Besides, you're ruthless.
You seem quite free now.
Why don't you play your curved knife?
If I do it well,
will you reward me?
Sure.
Of course.
What do you think?
Not bad.
I knew it.
Your moves are different from the ones from the Immortal Palace.
What do you plan to reward me?
I reward...
I reward you sending me a birthday present.
Since I am imprisoned here,
I'm afraid that's hard for me.
This is your business.
At least tell me
what's your name.
That's also your business.
I like smart people.
If you are smart,
I'll visit you again next time.
Smart people?
Interesting.
Your Majesty.
Mr. Tai.
Is everything ready?
Yes.
Are you in a hurry to use them?
Liu Shao was afraid that I'd suffer losses if I had a conflict with Luo Ge
and stopped him
so that I can leave.
But those people in the Immortal Palace
have been prejudiced against the Demons
and don't like Liu Shao.
Since she protected me like that,
I'm afraid they may vent their anger on her.
In this case,
you have to go to the Immortal Palace.
You may also see
if you can visit General Fu.
Is Immortal Tightwad
still angry?
Immortal.
Liu Shao is back.
Liu Shao hereby apologize to Immortal.
I admit
that I didn't protect Immortal,
but stop you and let He Na leave.
I know
Immortal was angry because the demons crossed the line.
But Immortal,
have you ever thought about it?
Marquis Wuyang's Mansion
keeps killing demons every year.
But the mortal world is still not peaceful.
It's not because Marquis Wuyang's Mansion is not strong enough,
but because the demons lack a king.
A king that can control them.
It's true.
Today, Immortal can give a warning to everyone by killing one demon.
But what if
they do it again in the future?
Will Immortal choose to kill them again?
If Immortal chooses counterviolence,
why do you need to cultivate your mind all the time?
Who are you?
How did you get in?
I...
I'm done.
I will kneel here for two hours.
Because I think kneeling for two hours
is enough for my fault.
I'll kneel then.
I kneeled.
Immortal.
Who told you to stand up?
Didn't you say you need to kneel for two hours?
Kneel down.
Wait.
Why is she here?
What did you do last night?
You've been here all night?
You care about it?
Of course I do!
You may leave.
Without my permission,
you can't enter Palace Chonghua in the future.
You're pretending.
Just keep pretending.
Keep your words.
Kneel here for two hours before you come to see me.
You and her...
That bad woman spent the whole night...
What does she want?
Who let you in?
You still have to kneel for 15 minutes.
Get out.
Serve tea.
Coming.
Who asked you to sit?
Bai Feng
is Lu Li's senior
but she's not a good person.
Why is she here?
Immortal Master sent her to serve in Palace Chonghua.
I can't refuse her.
Since you care so much,
I can stop her from coming to Palace Chonghua.
She'll only be in charge of the area around Xiyin Mountain.
That makes sense.
He Na came to the Immortal Palace.
I just received the news that
he seems to have arrived at the Litian Temple.
He said he wants to see me for pleading.
Did he come so fast
because he doesn't want you to suffer here?
You know that He Na
is very loyal to friends.
He treats Lu Li the same way.
Maybe you're right.
Counterviolence is not a long-term solution.
You have convinced me.
The demon world does need a king.
If you can persuade others in the Litian Temple,
I can consider teaching you magic
to protect those you want to protect.
Actually,
the person I want to protect the most is you.
But
I don't think you need my protection.
I'm so thirsty.
The Aquatic Demons is really talented.
How dare you come to the Immortal palace and bargain with us in public?
Do you think we
really forgot
what the Demon King did?
Although the former Demon King is guilty,
our clan has been living in the water
for ten thousand years.
You demons keep harming the mortal world.
Have you ever thought about stopping?
If Immortal Luo Ge hadn't arrived,
you would have destroyed Marquis Wuyang's mansion.
Immortal,
that's why I'm here today.
Tell me what you think.
Since our clan hid underwater,
those demons on land
split apart and entrenched separately.
They divided into four major clans.
When Ao Hen was alive,
her clan was the most powerful.
After her death,
they've been fighting each other.
Plus, they've been instigated by an unknown person.
That's why they repeatedly violated the realm
and harmed the human race.
Then what are you doing?
There is an unwritten rule in the demon world.
If you surrender to someone,
you have to give out your demon energy
and swear with blood
as a token of eternal obedience
and eternal loyalty.
You mean
you have subdued a clan?
Yes.
I've subdued the Northwest Demons.
I hereby swear
I will regain the glory of our clan
and become the real Demon King,
leading the demons
to live peacefully with the human race.
So this is your bargaining chip.
What do you want?
Demons won't offend the human race,
the human race should not offend us either.
Even if it's the immortal Palace,
they should treat our clan equally.
That's all?
I also want my brother,
Fu.
You demons never act in good faith.
Who knows what you’re up to?
Ge,
what do you think?
If you agree to
the idea the Demon King raised just now,
please step forward.
Looks like you're the only one who agrees.
Tell us what you think.
Immortal Master, do you think
among the three worlds,
the demon world is the worst
and that even if it will disappear,
it's not a pity?
It is known to all that
demons are despicable.
But why are there four seasons in the mortal world?
Spring, summer, autumn, and winter.
The winter is known for its coldness.
Should we also give it up?
Without winter hibernation,
there will not be the breeze in spring.
Little girl,
don't try to trap me.
The rule of the four seasons
is also true for the three worlds.
The demon world has been around for tens of thousands of years.
There must be a reason for their existence.
But it's also true that demons love killing cruelly.
I can't tolerate their killing.
I am incompetent.
But I know
in every battle between immortals and demons,
not only demons died,
but also the disciples of Immortal Palace.
But if the demon world is united,
the three worlds can avoid such casualties.
I agree with Liu Shao.
Master Shang.
Her words make sense.
Immortal Master,
don't you want to sacrifice less?
But these
are just your own ideas.
I also think
we shouldn't decide this with one person's opinion.
We should let everyone in the Immortal Palace decide.
I know.
Every year, the Immortal Palace will send people
to the mortal world to help Marquis Wuyang's Mansion kill demons.
I was once in Marquis Wuyang's Mansion
so I know you are the ones who are really in danger to kill demons.
They said it's a practice.
But you do know
how many immortal cultivators
die because of that every year.
If it's really like what He Na said,
there is a Demon King in the demon world,
and the demons will be restrained and stop rebelling.
Then you don't have to take any more risks.
Even if he fails,
will it be worse than now?
Why don't you let him try?
If anyone here
agrees to He Na's suggestion,
raise your hand.
Senior.
35 versus 35, even.
It's useless if we are even.
Dismiss.
I'll give you three years.
I want the letter of surrender from the four clans in the demon world.
If you can do it,
your brother will be free.
Ge...
OK.
36 versus 35.
Liu Shao won.
This is the responsibility of Immortal Palace.
It concerns the welfare of the three worlds,
not the winning or losing.
She won the heart of people.
You don't have to thank me.
You deserve
to be the Demon King of the Land.
I won't say thank you then.
Liu Shao.
Go back to Xiyin Mountain with me.
I'll go with you.
I want to see Fu.
No.
Your brother has always been cunning.
It's better not to see him.
Then I'll have a few more words with Liu Shao.
No.
Immortal.
I think...
You need to subdue four demon clans.
You must be busy.
I won't keep you today.
-I'm leaving. -Go.
Bye.
Hey,
can't you be quiet?
I'm quite quiet.
I just remembered something Lu Li said.
Do you want to hear it?
No.
Lu Li
once said
he liked fish slices in vinegar the most.
I think you
also like
fish slices in vinegar the most.
Sorry.
I missed the target just now.
You don't want to bully that girl,
so you bully me.
Lu Li is like that too.
Why do you want to see Wan Sui?
Luo Ning's birthday is in two days.
I promised to give her
the unique flowers in the three worlds.
Now you think of me.
Tell me.
What flowers do you want?
What do you have?
That's too many.
Listen carefully.
Red peony, green peony, hyacinth,
colourful embroidered ball, albizzia flowers, white camellia,
purple waterlily, and yucca rigida.
That's all?
Not satisfied?
So you want
a fancy way,
the grassroots style.
Then there is only the dog's tail grass.
I don't think Fairy has seen it before.
Still not satisfied?
That's all I have.
Well...
There is no flower
that Fairy has never seen in three worlds.
I have an idea.
Follow me.
Perfect.
You really forgot my birthday.
This month,
I won't talk to you.
Brother.
You are so busy
but you still found time to come here.
I guess
you must have
prepared an exquisite gift for your sister.
Goodness.
What did you say last time?
You said you will give me
the unique flowers
that I've never seen in three worlds.
Where's the gift?
What's wrong?
You don't want it?
If you don't want it, I'm going back.
Of course I want you to come.
It's my birthday today.
I'm not stupid.
Where are the unique flowers?
Liu Shao.
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
During the end of a season,
flowers will bloom beautifully,
cleaning off all the superficiality.
Hand in hand.
Spend the rest of life together.
This...
This is so beautiful.
Is this snowflake?
Liu Shao, look.
I've never seen
such a big
and beautiful snowflake.
This is not snowflake.
This is Weiyang flower.
Weiyang flower?
Liu Shao, is what you just said
the meaning of Weiyang flower?
So beautiful.
Do you like it?
I like it so much.
You're the best.
Luo Ning.
Liu Shao has prepared a banquet
in the garden.
See if you like it.
Okay.
Let's go, Liu Shao.
Let's go.
Brother, come on.
Let's go eat something delicious.
Darn it.
All these should be mine.
Liu Shao, try this.
Okay.
Let's drink.
How dare a demon sneak into the Xiyin Mountain?
Come and see me.
Who are you?
General Fu
from the Aquatic Demons.
The brother of the Demon King in White?
The demon aura in your body is hidden so well.
Did you use Lu Sheng’s magic weapon?
Unfortunately,
you can fool others,
but not me.
Even though I'm in decline now,
I'm still the descendant of the Demon King.
I can see the demon energy
in your body clearly.
I don't have any demon aura.
Don't try to trick me.
I'm not that stupid.
It's interesting.
The demon energy in your body is from Ao Hen.
You got a big advantage.
What do you want?
Did your master Lu Sheng
die recently?
How do you know?
Not only do I know,
I also know who killed him.
Who?
Is a very important person
celebrating the birthday today
in Xiyin Mountain?
The sister of Immortal Luo Ge,
Fairy Luo Ning.
Tell me
who killed my master.
Give this fairy a gift for me.
After that,
I'll tell you.
Slow down.
Liu Shao.
I like you so much.
Thank you
for giving me such a happy birthday.
As long as you are happy.
Let me tell you.
Are you okay?
No.
Brother.
You...
You like her.
I know.
What are you talking about?
Brother.
I'm so happy that you're back.
I finally don't have to look out every day
and miss you day by day.
I miss you so much.
I'm glad you're alive.
I...
Liu Shao.
My brother is really really good.
Am I right?
No.
Okay.
He's not
your brother.
He is my Lu Li.
Right.
Good taste.
You know what?
You had been with me
for so long in the mortal world.
You should
spend more time
with your sister.
Keep her company!
Keep her company.
No need to see me off.
Don't see me off.
Luo Ning.
Bye.